Queen Creek, AZ 85143 • (385) 236 8748 • rubiago.silveira@gmail.com Permanent Work Authorization | No Visa Sponsorship Needed

Rubiago Silveira

Motivated and tech-savvy individual with a diverse background in sales, construction labor, and epoxy technician, I am excited to transition into the field of front-end web development. I have an Associate's degree in integrated studies, a certificate in accounting and small business management, and experience in communication and leadership from my two-year missionary service. I am skilled in HTML, CSS, React, and JavaScript and fluent in English, Portuguese, and Spanish. My strong work ethic and adaptability make me a valuable asset to any tech team. I am eager to bring my unique skill set to the industry and to continue learning and growing as a developer.

KEY SKILLS

Strong Communication Skills	People Management
Solution seeker	Easily Adaptable
Process Improvement	Proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript, and React.js
Quality and Safety Management	Organization Skills

EDUCATION

•	Associate degree in Integrated Studies - Ensign College- UT	2021
•	Accounting Certificate - Ensign College- UT	2021
•	Small Business Management - Ensign College- UT	2021
•	Front End Developer Certificate - Meta Coursera - AZ	2022

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Gecko Garage Floors – AZ – Epoxy Technician trainer

11/2021 - 12/2022

- Demonstrated expertise in the installation and repair of epoxy and polyaspartic flooring, including surface preparation, mixing and application of materials, and final finishing. installation of epoxy and polyaspartic in garage floors.
- Provided exceptional customer service, effectively communicating project timelines, progress updates and addressing any concerns to ensure customers satisfaction.
- Contributed to the company's social media presence by gathering materials and creating content for instagram.
- Trained and mentored new employees, leading to increased productivity and efficiency in the team.
- Demonstrated attention to the detail and problem-solving skills by identifying and resolving issues that arose during the installation process.

Ion Solar – UT– Canvasser / appointment setter

12/2020 - 11/2021

- Demonstrated exceptional sales and persuasion skills, closing deals with more than 50% of prospects visited through door-to-door sales efforts.
- Excellent in communicating and negotiating with potential customers to schedule appointments, answering questions and addressing concerns to establish trust and build relationships.
- Managed time effectively to meet daily and weekly goals, and consistently exceeded them.

Ivory Homes – Utah – Construction Assistant

04/2019 - 12/2020

- worked effectively as part of a team, communicating and collaborating with others construction workers to complete projects on time and under budget.
- demonstrated the ability to adapt to changing situations, work in a flexible manner, and complete tasks under tight deadlines.